{
    "subject": "resource/The_Automatic",
    "predicate": "ontology/bandMember",
    "object": "resource/Paul_Mullen",
    "human_readable": "Paul Mullen is a band member of The Automatic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9663141369819641,
            "question": "What band is Paul Mullen a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9235007762908936,
            "question": "Name one band that Paul Mullen is associated with."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9119990468025208,
            "question": "Has Paul Mullen released any music with The Automatic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8731205463409424,
            "question": "Is Paul Mullen a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8424403071403503,
            "question": "Who is Paul Mullen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8299573659896851,
            "question": "What is the name of the band that Paul Mullen belongs to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.769334614276886,
            "question": "To what musical group does Paul Mullen belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5914795398712158,
            "question": "What instrument does Paul Mullen play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4306378662586212,
            "question": "What genre of music is The Automatic known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13470038771629333,
            "question": "Where did The Automatic gain popularity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Mullen is a band member of The Automatic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5043_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is The Automatic known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5043_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instrument does Paul Mullen play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5043_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what musical group does Paul Mullen belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5043_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5043_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Paul Mullen's involvement with various bands, including yourcodenameis:milo and Young Legionnaire. However, they also mention that he replaced Alex Pennie as a member of The Automatic (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5043/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt). This suggests that Paul Mullen is indeed a band member of The Automatic, albeit not one of the founding members. \n\nTherefore, based on the context information provided, the answer to whether the triple \"Paul Mullen is a band member of The Automatic\" is correct according to the documents is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Paul Mullen joined The Automatic after Alex Pennie left and was involved as vocals, guitar, and synthesiser."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}